coolopticalillusions.com 2017-05-23

# Privacy Policy | Cool Optical Illusions - Amazing Optical Illusions!

## Our Commitment to Privacy

We understand that you value your privacy. We also value your privacy and seek to explain how we use any data that we may have gathered.

#### Type of information we may collect:

If you complete our feedback form or interact with us, we will collect and store only the information that you knowingly provide, such as Name, Website, Email Address, and the message. This information is stored in a secure database and may also be accessible on personal computers or stored on email servers. However we currently have no intention of using this information, other than basic communication with you, or to help find relavant information that my be of interest to you (and others) on this website.

#### How we use your information (Google Adsense):

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

### Google Analytics

We do also use google analytics (and occassionally other analytics type programs). These generally gather your information along with thousands of other users, and are used mainly to decide what areas of the site to promote. To learn more about google’s privacy policy, you may do so here: Google analtyics [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html).

### Valueclick Media

We may also use Valueclick or other vendors to provide advertising. [Valueclick privacy policy](http://www.valueclickmedia.com/about/privacy/display-web-user).

### Contact Us

If you have any specific questions about our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.coolopticalillusions.com/contact-us.htm).
